crowd1.com 2019-12-02

# CROWD1 - Impossible is nothing!

#### This privacy policy is for this website www.crowd1.com and served by Crowd1 Network Limited - Crowd1 and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

## The Website

This website and it's owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure and improper use of your information, we have established appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect in accordance with our privacy policy.

If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. Crowd1 handles all of this data with the utmost confidentiality.

## Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer/device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for website to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer/device.

Cookies are small files saved to the user's computer's hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.

Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website onto their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website.

This website uses tracking software to monitor it's visitors to better understand how they use it. One of the software are provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage.

The software will save a cookie to your computer's hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.

You can read Google's privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/privacy.html) for further information.

## Revocation

You may revoke your consent to receiving promotional offers at any time by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5c2f292c2c332e281c3f2e332b386d723f3331).

## Transfer of personal data

Crowd1 will transfer your data exclusively for the purpose of processing your orders and/or giving you access to the infrastructure (e.g. servers, IT services, web hosting) of service providers commissioned by us. These service providers will process your data strictly in compliance with our instructions and will be supervised by us. Such service providers are strictly prohibited from using the data collected and processed through the Crowd1 website for their own purposes.

If you are interested in our products or in participating in a Crowd1 business opportunity and ask for establishing a contact, we will transmit the personal data you have entered in the form to an Associate in order to allow him to advise you on the opportunities offered by Crowd1 or on our products.

If you are interested in participating in a Crowd1 contact to purchase our products or services, you will be contacted by the Associate for this purpose.

## Cross-border transfer

Your personal data may be transferred to another group company affiliated with Crowd1 if this is necessary for the implementation of the object of the respective contract and/or for the execution of your orders or for the provision of a service. Some of the companies of the Crowd1 group may be located outside the European Economic Area and be governed by different statutory data protection provisions, or by none at all. In such case, Crowd1 assures that it will take appropriate measures in order to ensure sufficient and reasonable data protection also in such case. You may contact Crowd1 at any time regarding your right of information or any other rights.

## External websites

Our websites may contain links to websites operated by other companies. If you use such links, you will leave the website of Crowd1. Crowd1 is not responsible for such third-party websites. The Crowd1 Privacy Policy does not apply to websites of third parties. Please check directly on such websites how such protected personal data are used.

## Modification of data and right of information

If you wish to verify, rectify or delete personal data made available to us at an earlier date, you may contact us at any time by email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please state in your request exactly what data are concerned. We will process your request as soon as possible.

At your request, Crowd1 will inform you whether and what personal data are saved about you with us.

## Adjustment of the data protection provisions

Crowd1 shall be entitled to modify these data protection provisions. The registered users will be informed of any such modifications. The modified provisions shall apply to all new users with immediate effect. For existing users such adjusted provisions shall become effective within a period of 30 days from their announcement, unless they have been objected to in writing.

## Data security

Crowd1 uses technical and organizational security measures in order to protect your data administrated by us against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or access by unauthorized persons. Our security measures are regularly improved in accordance with the state of technological developments. The processing and transfer of data are made by the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) procedure.

## Contact & Communication 

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products we offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
